

Summary _

Software Engineer specializing in fullstack web development. Interested in problem solving through code. I enjoy doing a variety of hobbies and reading various subjects.

Skills_

Proficient JavaScript/TypeScript, HTML & CSS, SASS, Express, React, Redux, NodeJS, MongoDB, Webpack, Grunt, Gulp, Git

Knowledgeable Electron, Rust, Actix-Web, Elixir, Phoenix, Ecto, PostgreSQL

Basic C, C++, Java, Lisp, Haskell, ŁTFX, Web Assembly, AWS, Docker, D3

Work Experience _____

Lifion by ADP New York City

FULLSTACK PLATFORM ENGINEER Feb. 2019 - PRESENT

• Building a data mapper that is used for Lifion's low code platform

ITN Networks New York City

FRONT END ENGINEER

Jul. 2018 - Mar. 2019

- Worked on various features on the company's front end codebase with over 1.5 million lines of code with 10 other engineers using React
- Integrated Cypress testing automation and developed a more reliable end to end testing infrastructure
- Aggressively refactored the codebase to improve performance, readability and maintainability

IrisVR Inc.

New York City

FULLSTACK SOFTWARE ENGINEER CONSULTANT

Oct. 2016 - Mar. 2018

- $\bullet \ \ \text{Implemented build system on company's front end and desktop app development environment using Webpack}$
- Developed the company's front end client using React and Redux
- Developed the company's desktop client using Electron and React
- · Designed failure-point handling to handle disconnections between several NodeJS backend services gracefully
- Migrated company's MongoDB and AWS Redshift database changes with ensured consistency

Ninthbeat Inc. New York City

CO-FOUNDER & FULLSTACK SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Mar. 2015 - Dec. 2015

- · Built a marketplace platform for musicians to buy and sell their used musical instruments
- Utilized MEAN stack to develop a full-stack solution for the platform
- Develop a smartphone facing client using Ionic
- Integrated Firebase to be used as a real-time client chat feature

Education

Queens College Flushing, NY

M.A. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE (3.9 GPA) 2016 - 2018

Alliance Theological Seminary Manhattan, NY

M.Div. in Theological Studies 2010 - 2013

Bina Nusantara University

Jakarta, Indonesia

B.Eng. in Industrial Engineering 2004 - 2008

August 8, 2019 Christian Sakai · Résumé 1